bigrockwebdirectory.com 2012-12-03

# Contact us at BigRockWebDirectory.com

**BigRockWebDirectory.com Privacy Policy**

**_BigRockWebDirectory.com_**  is committed to protecting your privacy online.  Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We sometimes use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to customize your experience on  ** _BigRockWebDirectory.com_**.

In general, you can visit  ** _BigRockWebDirectory.com  _**on the World Wide Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc.  ** _BigRockWebDirectory.com  _**uses this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site.

To become a member of **_BigRockWebDirectory.com  _**you must provide us with certain information such as your real name and email address. This information will not be sold or shared with any third party. All information gathered is used for internal purposes only by **_BigRockWebDirectory.com._**

We use some outside companies to display adverts on this site. These adverts may use  cookies. Cookies received with adverts are collected by these outside companies, and we do not have access to this information.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**_BigRockWebDirectory.com_**  has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users.  
**  
** This site contains links to other sites.   _ **BigRockWebDirectory.com**_  is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.   ** _BigRockWebDirectory.com_**  has no control over, and is not responsible other sites which collect your information and then refer you to ** _BigRockWebDirectory.com_**.

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by  ** _BigRockWebDirectory.com_**  as outlined in this Privacy Policy.  If you sign up for services on  ** _BigRockWebDirectory.com_**  then you must also agree to the specific Terms and Conditions for those services.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.
